stripersonline.com 2010-06-28

# Privacy Policy - StripersOnline.com - Privacy Promise

* * *

For all [StripersOnline.com](http://www.stripersonline.com/) web pages and features.   
For all [StripersOnline Online Catalog](http://www.stripersonline.net/cart/shop/index.html) web pages and features.   
**Effective 8/30/2000**

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

* * *

**Our Commitment To Privacy  **

> Your privacy is extremely important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:  **

> This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the StripersOnline website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register for access to some of the many features. At no time is any information collected that you do not submit yourself!  The types of personal information collected at these pages can possibly include some or all of the following, but will be clearly stated at the submission point: 
> 
> Name   
>  Address   
>  Email address   
>  Phone number   
>  Credit/Debit Card Information 
> 
> SurfTalk, the message board on StripersOnline uses cookies **only** to store your preferences, login, and password. No information is collected, tracked, or shared from those cookies. No other portion of this web site, as of today, uses cookies in any fashion. Our online shopping cart does not take, store, or utilize any information from cookies. It requires extra effort on this end to use, but for your peace of mind and security shopping, we chose to use this cookie-less shopping cart. If in the future we are to change or add any software that utilizes cookies that it stores on your computer, you will be notified here of those changes and they will be explained in the greatest detail possible. We take your comfort and security while visiting our website to be an extremely serious matter and will make every effort to keep you fully informed of every change.

**The Way We Use Information:  **

> We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties...it is not sold, traded, made available, or stored in any area that could be violated online. This information is not stored on your computer by a cookie set by the ordering process or any other process that takes place at StripersOnline. 
> 
> We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are never used for any other purpose and are not shared, sold, traded, or made available to any outside parties. You have our word on this, we do not welcome advertisers that wish to capture data about our visitors. We do not use or allow software that would store or make available to third parties this information. Again, we take your privacy as a very serious concern.
> 
> You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. Simply ordering at StripersOnline will never cause any other process to take place. You are not automatically added to a mailing list, your name does not go in any online database for others to see. Your orders and all info submitted here are held strictly between StripersOnline and you.
> 
> We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Demographics are important in this business, but not so important that any specific information about any individual visitor ever leaves here.
> 
> Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. **All information that is submitted or left behind from your visit to StripersOnline will not leave StripersOnline, it won't be sold, traded, or made available to anyone for any reason.** *
> 
> (*The only time that any of this information will be made available is in the unlikely even that it is officially requested, by subpoena, from the police or other government agency so entitled to demand this information. Also, in the event that StripersOnline should find it necessary for whatever reason to take legal action against a visitor, any necessary personal information required to successfully prosecute will be made available to the police and/or courts. These are the only two event in which personal information would leave here.) 

**Our Commitment To Data Security  **

> To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. No personal information is stored online, it is all stored locally on PC's. All online purchases are made through a Verisign Encrypted server (certificate information available by request).

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:  **

> Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. This may change in the future as we think it important to educate these younger fishermen at an early age. Any areas that will attract those 13 years and younger will have special precautions taken to handle their personal information in such a manner that it will never made public. Also, anyone 13 years and younger are required to have a parent submit to StripersOnline a completed and signed permission slip (available by request) stating that they acknowledge and accept the fact that their child is actively participating or intending to participate in our forum and/or chat room. As these changes take place, this notice will be updated to reflect them. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information  **

> You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online by sending an email to the [**webmaster**](mailto:webmaster@StripersOnline.com) here requesting such info. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. Corrections to this information are largely unnecessary as the information is not stored online and is updated only through the ordering process. If you would like to change any factual personal information, please send to the above email address a request that credibly shows the error.
> 
> To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us  **

>   Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at **(732) 361-7412** between 9am and 8pm or send us an email at **[webmaster@stripersonline.com](mailto:webmaster@stripersonline.com) **
> 
> You can also reach us by mail at the following address:  
>  **StripersOnline.com  
>  102 Bennett Road  
>  Shark River Hills, NJ  
>  07753**  
> 

* * *

*If you feel this information can be of value to others, please feel free to link directly to this page - the URL to link to is shown in your browser window.

SurfTalk Fishing Forums  | Saltwater Fishing Articles | Photo Pages | [Striped Bass Fishing - StripersOnline](http://www.stripersonline.com/ "Striped bass fishing, striper fishing, surf fishing and saltwater fishing resources.") | [ Online Tackle Store](http://www.stripersonline.net/cart/shop/index.html "Striped bass fishing tackle, striper fishing tackle, lures for striped bass, surf fishing tackle, Choopy Lures, Gibbs lures, darters, needlefish, rigged eels and more.") | [SurfChat -Fishing chat!](http://www.stripersonline.com/SurfChat/ "Real time chat with other striped bass fishing and surf fishing folks.")  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Additional Resources | Rockfish Cartoons | Striped Bass Archives | e-Surf Auction |  [Fishing Reports](http://www.stripersonline.net/forms/reports_2000.htm "Where are the stripers now, striped bass fishing reports, fishing reports.") | Tide Chart  | Fishing Books   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
Conservation | Weather | Striped Bass Length Weight Charts | SurfTalk Fish Photos | Marine Forecast  | Weekend Warrior   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
Copyright© **Tim Surgent** and **www.stripersonline.com** 1999-2010. All rights reserved.  
StripersOnline.com - We'll help you catch more fish!  
This page was last updated on January 8, 2010   
We take your privacy very seriously.  
See our **Privacy Notice** for details.
